This is Trigun.
Oh, my God.
Hey, Bash.
Now everything that brought
you and Rem together is gone.
Is that your excuse for killing?
Haven't you learned anything
over the past hundred years?
You can't even regenerate the
scars they carved into your body.
It's symbolic of your foolish
waste of energy on this garbage.
And it's not your right to
decide whether they live or die.
They deserve a chance!
What's the use in growing up if the only
thing that grows is your sentimentalism?
You're still a
good-for-nothing pathetic whip!
What is that?
This is what we're capable of.
It's time to take this garbage
and get rid of it forever!
Are you made of me again?
Are you actually aiming at me again?
Eriks? Eriks?
How long are you planning
on staying in bed, Eriks?
Come on now, get up! Eriks?
Come on, you gotta let us on this bus.
You might try and take
this town. I have money.
Let me on this bus while we're standing
here arguing it could be too late.
You need a ticket to ride,
mister, and I don't give a go.
What's the matter with you?
Don't you get it yet?
Just leave your price, I'll pay anything.
There sure seems to be an awful
lot of tension in this town.
Haven't seen you before.
I take it you just arrived. That's right.
Well, you have my sympathy because
you're never going to leave this town.
What happened over there?
This town has been completely
taken over by bandits.
And to make matters worse,
they say that crazy fella Vash
the Stampede is running the show.
The sheriff went out to
negotiate with the varmints,
but when he came back, he had
doubled his weight in lead.
Walking into this town is like
walking into a giant spider's web.
The legendary gunman's behind this?
What do you think?
Do you believe it?
I don't know what to think.
He is the man who turned
two of the seven cities into
ashes and was called mankind's
first localized disaster.
Some folks say he put that
huge crater in the moon.
I guess you'd have to
be nuts to believe that.
Anyway,
whether the legend is true or not,
the one thing I do know is this
town is in some big trouble.
By the way, friend, what is that thing?
I'm a traveling priest.
Well, that's good timing.
You'll be useful here.
Don't need anything formal, just
some help with the funerals.
They took out the chaplain a while back.
What's the big idea you guys?
Oh, it's only Lena.
You know what's the big hurry?
Was wondering if you
could hide me somewhere?
What'd you do this time?
She doesn't know when to quit.
Fun.
That's all the guys.
A pedophile.
He deserved a good thump.
Not really.
All he did was grab a rear end.
Will you keep your mouth shut?
What are you telling me?
Oh, my dear.
Yeah, I'm afraid so, and they
weren't real happy about it,
but at least I don't think
they saw me come in here.
Hey, that's not funny, kid.
If what she says is true...
Hey, I wasn't done eating yet.
All right!
Where's a little girl who
struck my face with her heel?
She's got a price to pay
and I'm here to collect!
That heel looks more
like a whole footprint.
Quiet, you!
I can see why he's upset.
It does ruin his boyish good looks.
This guy says he saw her enter that bar!
If he's wrong, he's dead!
Why?
Because I like to kill scum
who waste my precious time!
In any event, this problem will be settled
in approximately three miniscule seconds!
Three, two, one, he dies!
Eriks, wait a second!
What do you think you're doing?
Oh, hey, hi there, Mr. Bandit Man.
We're sorry you didn't find it that funny.
I just wanted to say that she's
only a little 12-year-old.
Come on now, have a heart, won't you?
Send out the kid now or else!
I'm afraid that's not an option.
Looks like you want to kill her
or cause her some kind of harm.
I won't even ask for a free favor.
How about if I do this?
Will you let her off the hook?
Eriks?
Sorry, but that's not
good enough, blondie.
If you're gonna go down on all fours,
the least you can do is act like a dog?
and I expect some real commitment.
Naturally, that means getting naked.
All right.
It's a deal.
You've got to keep your word.
I can't let you do this,
Eriks! Please stop!
You don't have to do it!
Eriks!
Eriks...
Oh, my God.
It's not your fault, kid.
He's got his reasons.
We've gotta trust that
he knows what he's doing.
But why?
That's just the way he is.
I'm gonna thank you for the canine tricks!
I've decided to give you a nice big tip!
Let's go!
Shoot him!
Eriks!
Oh, what happened to this man?
He's been shot!
You gotta help him! Eriks again.
What's happened this time?
I can't tell if the bull
is still inside him, Doc.
If you had to choose between your life and
your pride, what do you think you'd do?
I don't know, but I would never
strip butt naked and bark like a dog.
Talent like that comes
easy for a wimp like Eric.
If there weren't for that
wimp, you two would be dead!
Eric's!
My poor Eric's.
It's all right, Grandma.
They were able to get the
bullet out of him safely.
I'll never understand him.
He's one lucky devil.
I don't know who this
legendary gunman thinks he is,
but what in the hell gives him the right?
to steal what precious
little family I have left?
Damn him, anyway!
Hey, hey, easy there.
Now don't go doing that.
You won't last two seconds
against him, don't you understand?
Oh, let me go!
All right, how about
you going to my place?
See?
You're all a bunch of cowards,
You weak young whippersnappers.
Have no right to order me around!
You're gonna get yourself
killed, you stupid old bat!
Oh, shut your mouth.
Grandma, don't say that.
I can't, Lina.
All of this is my fault.
If I had just stayed away
from them, he wouldn't have.
He wouldn't have.
I'm so sorry, Eric.
If you're quite finished here, could
you please keep the noise down?
There are other patients here.
Please forgive me, doctor.
I understand how you feel.
You don't need to worry.
I'll have Eric's move
to the ward right away.
Thank you, Doctor.
Lena, let's fetch him a change of clothes.
Okay.
Let's move him and get
this place cleaned up.
Oh, hello.
Sorry I didn't see you there.
He'll be all right now, I assure you.
I know that, no problem.
I just stopped by to
see if I could help out.
You just gonna sleep?
Snap out of it!
What the hell are you doing to him?
He needed it! Doctor! Look
at that! Oh my gosh! Hey!
What an amazing recovery.
You've regained consciousness so quickly.
Excuse me, Doctor, but could you
leave the room for a little while?
Well, yes, I suppose.
Don't let him strain
himself, you understand?
Well, it's been a long
time, Vash the Stampede.
I finally found you, you dumb jerk.
What's a legendary guy like
you doing in a place like this?
You have no idea what I've been through.
I could have destroyed this entire
planet with that angel arm of mine.
It gets worse.
There's a loss of memory.
I don't remember what I did.
That may be true, but you
do know you did it, right?
Oh yeah, I know.
I have fragmented visions,
but more than anything, there's an ache
in my heart that tells me I did it.
I know I'm the one who put
the hole in the fifth moon.
It was me.
Okay so you did this terrible
thing now what are you so
afraid of what you can do you're
living an easy retirement no
it's just that i want to live
quietly for once so i decided
to change my name and my way of
life why are you here wolfwood
what brings you to this town
are you hanging it around for
a good laugh actually i came to
take you away away where well
if you're asking me for a final
destination i have absolutely
no idea however the one thing
i do know is i need your help
i spent a lot of time combing
through augusta trying to find you
does the name frank marlin happen to ring
a bell all i did was mention your name
and he fix the gun for free maybe why give
it to me huh i thought you might need it
what i need what i want is to
live my life here with them
why was he hospitalized the last
time lena he tried to stop a
violent drunk at at the bar and
ended up getting punched himself.
And what about the time before that?
He fell off at Thomas.
Oh, be sure you remember to thank him.
I know, I'll remember, Grandma.
Hello there, are you okay?
You're in horrible shape you poor thing.
You must have been through
an awful lot. It's okay.
You'll be safe here
Don't worry.
We'll take good care of you
So you're staying here, huh?
Whenever I do anything
people die, all right.
If you want this pathetic
little existence so bad
that you'd give up everything
else then go for it.
By the way are
you familiar
with the town called Carcasses?
It's a tiny town on the
southern Cornelia region.
Something really strange
happened there about six
months ago.
Seems the entire population suddenly
disappeared without a trace.
There was no sign of even
the slightest struggle.
Everything in town looked
completely normal except that all the
people had vanished like a mirage.
They
sent in the cavalry and searched the
place over but didn't find a soul.
One
cavalryman did discover
something very odd though.
There was a man's name, painted on the
monument in the middle of the town square.
It was one word, carefully written in red,
Knives.
Damn you, Knives.
It doesn't seem to
matter how far I travel.
My destiny is always followed
by blood and gun smoke.
The result is the same every time.
Mountains of death and debris.
You've got to come with us, Rem!
Please don't leave us!
Dash, take care of nerves!
No, Rem!
Come back!
What?
What should I do?
Your gun!
Give me your gun!
Hurry!
Grandma Cheryl, what?
What is it?
It's Lena!
They got her! What? How?
Just give it to me, now! Stop!
You'll throw your life away!
Besides, they've probably
already killed her!
Shut up!
Don't argue with me!
Just give me the gun!
Cheryl, Cheryl, wait!
You know, I was kind of
fond of my new life here.
I really hate to leave.
Sorry, them's the brakes.
Someone's got to get tough around here or
those maniacs are going
to destroy this town.
They're both gone!
Please don't follow us.
Tell everyone to stay where they are.
We've gone to get Lena.
By themselves?
How many are there?
About 200.
100 for each of us, huh? Yep.
Well, that's not exactly fair to them.
Hey, I don't want you
killing anyone, alright?
Why don't you just ask me not to breathe?
Thou shalt not kill, remember?
What kind of church man are you anyway?
Whoa, deja vu, I've heard that before.
Now you're starting to
sound like you ain't so...
Eric!
Time to kill!
Showtime!
Why did I have to go and talk
to someone this filthy anyway?
What was I thinking?
I guess I must be crazy.
What a mess.
How the hell did those two manage to take
care of all them thugs by themselves?
I have no idea.
I've never seen anyone
so horrifyingly strong.
So your mind is made up, then?
Yes, I'm sorry.
It's time I go.
Even though I hate to
do this to you and Lina.
Isn't there anything we can do, Eriks?
Maybe if you'd tell me about
it, I could help somehow.
Thank you, but I can't.
Because you see, if I did, I'd only
be putting you and Lina in danger.
Here you have a home.
You could end up alone again
with no one there to help.
That's what worries us the
most about your leaving.
I'm sorry.
Who would have guessed that
Eriks was Vash the Stampede?
Unbelievable.
Yeah, tell me about it.
And to think that all this time we were
convinced that this pig man was Vash.
So, you think the legendary gunman's
gonna stick around these parts?
Shoot, don't even go there.
Haven't we suffered enough?
Yeah, we oughta run him out right now.
She cried, huh?
That's a shame.
I didn't know.
Gee, no, I feel bad.
I guess maybe I was acting
just a little bit too pushy.
You don't need to apologize.
Mr.
Preacher, please take good care of Eriks.
Unlike you, he's a bumbling fool of a
goody-goody and a sweet, gentle soul.
Lena and I have always
known somewhere deep
in our hearts it was too good to be true.
We knew Eriks would probably
have to leave us someday.
Yet we chose not to believe it.
Bless him.
It doesn't change the fact that
we're losing a member of the family.
Please, Mr.
Wolfwood, don't forget that.
I'm truly sorry.
I really am.
I'm sorry, Grandma.
There.
It's all done.
Lena.
Thank you for everything.
I only wanted to keep you safe.
But somehow, it turned
out the other way around.
I was too weak.
Don't be ridiculous.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
No, Lina.
It's me who should be saying that.
Lina, thank you, and goodbye for now.
In the blue sky, the
wind is in the future.
The light of the day of the sky,
as you can see,
as you can see?
Let's go.
I'll see you
next time.
Strong will can stir the heart,
but a will too strong can cut
off the heart's visibility.
The sorrow of a man bereaved
of his family turns into hate,
which eventually metamorphoses
into the intent to kill.
The man's finger reaches for the trigger.
Sins change people.
Sin begets sin.
But I, I still want to believe.
I want to believe in the heart,
the heart that feels the sin.